O.k.
now on this time imagine that your opponent isn't that strong of a server .You're, you're turning your second serve or you're, you've really; you've got a pretty good serve return.
So we're going to do the topspin forehand serve return now.
So Ken's going to demonstrate this, but I'm going to serve to him.
So what I want you to think about is here imagine I'm returning serve to my forehand, so I have the racket in my forehand position; forehand grip and I turn, now because it's a serve there's a lot of pace on it.
I don't need to take this huge turn, but I just turn and then I want to hit the ball like that.
So I'm trying to maybe win the point with this return or just hit a nice force, tough return which puts them in a weak position so then I can bring the point maybe on the next shot or the shot after.
So Ken's going to demonstrate forehand topspin serve return.
And it's a great shot to work on, and you can win a lot of points if you get a good return.
Good; try it again.
Oh that ball had some muster on it!
So as you can see you just do this drill and you're going to get a pretty good return and your opponent knows that if you can return their serve their in a lot, their in a very tough; tough hole because then they don't have any weapons.
So if you can return a serve it really makes you that much more of a deadly player because a serve is usually a main weapon for a lot of players, and if you can return it pretty effortlessly it makes holding your serve that much easier.